question_data = [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Water is naturally coloured blue.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Furby was released in 1998.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Only a small percentage of the world&#039;s population is lactose intolerant.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "This is the correct spelling of &quot;Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]